porned.com 2011-10-07

# Porned.com - FREE High quality full length Porn!

Privacy Policy

Site owner does not provide any facility for sending or receiving private or confidential electronic communications. For purposes of privacy of communications only, all messages transmitted to site owner shall be deemed to be readily accessible to the general public. Visitors should not use this site to transmit any communication for which the sender intends only the sender and the intended recipient(s) to read. Notice is hereby given that all messages entered into this site can and may be read by the operators of this service, regardless of whether or the operators are the intended recipients of such messages.

Our privacy policy is entirely advisory, and we shall not be subject to any legal action for violations hereof. With that caveat, our privacy policy is as follows:

**What kind of information do you collect?**  
When you join the membership portion of our web site you are asked to provide your name, address, e-mail, username and password, credit card number and expiration date, and birth date. When you participate in special events such as contests and polls, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail, username and password, and birth date. When users request pages from our server, our Web server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses. We also collect information regarding your use of our site through the use of cookies. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We often maintain a record or notes of communications with you regarding your account. In addition, any other information you transmit to us may be collected. 

**Who sees my information?**  
We do not, and will not, distribute, rent or sell any personally identifiable information to third parties without your express consent, other than as necessary to process your credit card payment or take steps against fraud. We may also share your information with our lawyers, accountants, and other professionals to the extent necessary for legitimate business purposes. We may also share your information as part of a takeover, asset purchase, asset sale, merger, or similar transaction. Within the virtual world there may be other merchants or entities with a contractual or other relationship with us and to the extent necessary to facilitate a seamless user experience within the virtual world; we may share such information to the extent necessary to effectuate this goal. In addition, note that if we believe you are engaging in illegal activity or activity in violation of this agreement, we may in our discretion share that information as required to rectify or take action with regard to that activity. Also note our policy on reporting illegal activity (described below) supersedes any privacy policy we have.

**How do you use my information?**  
We use you information in order to process your credit card payment, to facilitate your viewing of our web site and to communicate with you. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and web site usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally. We use your e-mail address to send occasional e-mail newsletters and promotional e-mail to you about services and products offered by us or by other parties which we feel may be of interest to you. We will not spam you and honor all removal requests immediately.

**How secure is my information?**  
Site owner takes reasonable precautions to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about you. We provide you with a secure web page through which to submit your billing information when you join the membership portion of our web site. We maintain your personally identifiable information in a reasonably secure manner including storing such information behind firewalls.

**I've got more questions - can you help?**  
Site owner recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this web site or your dealings with this site, please contact us:

By mail:  
Porned.com  
#341 – 280 Nelson Street  
Vancouver, BC V6B 2E2  
Canada  

Or by telephone at: (877) 349-4752 or for International callers 1 + (778) 329-9959.

Please note that persons under the age of 18 are prohibited from viewing our web site, and site owner does not collect any personal information from persons under the age of 18. Please also note that site owner is not responsible for the content or the privacy polices of web sites to which it may provide links or the websites of its advertisers.

|
